High school is about to get a make-over.
Bratz is a comedy, music, family film directed by Sean McNamara.
The popular Bratz dolls come to life in their first live-action feature film.
Finding themselves being pulled further and further apart, the fashionable four band together to fight peer
pressure, learn what it means to stand up for your friends, be true to oneself and live out your dreams.
Sasha, played by Logan Browning.
Jade, played by Janel Parrish.
Yasmin, played by Nathalia Ramos.
Cloe, played by Skyler Shaye.
Meredith, played by Chelsea Kane.
Avery, played by Anneliese Van Der Pol.
Bratz (also known as Bratz: The Movie) is a 2007 American teen comedy film based
on the fashion dolls of the same name from MGA Entertainment.
The film is directed by Sean McNamara with a screenplay by Susan Estelle
Jansen, from a story written by Adam de la Peña and David Eilenberg.
It is the first live-action film based on the doll line after numerous
direct-to-video animated films and a television series.
It stars Nathalia Ramos, Skyler Shaye, Logan Browning and Janel Parrish as the members of the
group, with Chelsea Staub, Lainie Kazan, and Jon Voight in supporting roles.
The story revolves around a group of four teenage girls, the origin of their friendship, and the
social pyramid that tries to make the Bratz conform to archetypal high school cliques.
Principal photography took place in Los Angeles in February and March 2007.
Bratz was released in the United States on August 3, 2007, by Lionsgate.
It received negative reviews and grossed $26 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of high school, female friendship,
based on toy, teenage girl, duringcreditsstinger.
The tone is lighthearted.